Lisa Groen

+31 (0)6 4549 - 1808 lisatgroen@hotmail.com Amsterdam, Noord-Holland, the Netherlands

https://github.com/Lisaag https://www.linkedin.com/in/lisa-groen-bb298816b/

Master student Game and Media Technology at Utrecht University. Mostly experienced within the field of game development and VR/AR development. Open to learning all kinds of skills within the field of software engineering. Likes to spend her free time playing the electric guitar in a band and playing video games and tabletop games.

SKILLS

Programming Languages	C#C++Python	HLSL (shader language)HTML, CSS, Javascript
Tools/Libraries	UnityUnreal EngineGame MakerVisual Studio (Code)	Blender, MayaMicrosoft AzureOpenCL, OpenGL, OpenCV

EDUCATION

02/2023 - Present

Game and Media Technology (Master's)

Utrecht University – Utrecht

- Computer Vision (Machine Learning, Keras, OpenCV)
- Software Optimization (GPGPU, OpenCL, SIMD)
- 3D model feature vector extraction, clustering
- Mathematics (Linear Algebra, Calculus, Statistics)

11/2021 - 12/2022

Japanese Language

Academy of Language Arts – Tokyo, Iidabashi

- Focused on learning Japanese Language for daily and business usage
- Conversational and written Japanese (speaking, reading, writing)

09/2016 - 08/2020

HBO-ICT - Game Development (Bachelor's)

Amsterdam University of Applied Sciences – Amsterdam

- Focused on learning a broad set of different skills within the field of ICT, focussed on Game Development.
- Object Oriented languages (C#, C++, Java)
- Game Engines (Unity, Unreal Engine, Game Maker)
- Web development, Embedded systems and IoT development, Game development and VR/AR development.

EXPERIENCE

09/2023 - Present

Chair, U-pad (student association) – Utrecht https://u-pad.nl

- Delegating tasks, attending meetings, organizing events
- Communication with members and externals

01/2021 - 10/2021

AR software engineer, Miracle Mile – Tokyo, Chiyoda-ku

https://miraclemile-inc.com/

- Mobile AR development (Apple, Android)
- AR development for head mounted hardware (Hololens 2)
- IoT development using Arduino and M5Stack combined with Microsoft's Hololens 2.
- Realtime online cross-platform application development
- Microsoft Azure

03/2020 - 08/2020

Game programmer intern, Shinyuden - Tokyo, Chiyoda-ku https://www.shinyuden.com/

- Creating a procedurally generated 3D world environment inside Unity Engine.
- Game concepting and design
- General game programming (C#, Unity Engine)
- Shader programming

09/2019 - 01/2020

VR software engineer intern, Therapieland - Amsterdam

https://therapieland.nl/

- VR software development (HTC Vive)
- Procedural mesh generation
- Game concepting and design
- Secondary Research
- 3D modeling

01/2018 - 07/2018

Software engineer intern, Digital Society School – Amsterdam https://digitalsocietyschool.org/

- Secondary research
- Concept creation, prototyping and peer testing
- Static website development (HTML, CSS)
- Interactive bracelet creation (Arduino, C)

Languages

• Dutch (native)

English (fluent)

Japanese (JLPT N2)